[{"answer": "I was actually at work, and I got a text message from one of my boys' parents on my soccer team asking me if we've been evacuated and not knowing what was going on, I turned the radio on and by that time we were already in the mandatory evacuation, so I ended up locking up the gym early, speeding down the Black Forest to grab the dog.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "When did you learn that this was so serious?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, I was at work but the only he was able to grab was the dogs.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "What did you have with you?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "It was pretty tough by the time I got back to (INAUDIBLE), the police closed it off and I got out of my car and I asked them listen, I have three dogs, it will take me five minutes to get down there, I'll be back within a flash and he told me that I was risking my own life and obviously did what I have to do for our family.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "How tough was it?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "I mean, I wanted to have a meltdown.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "What were you feeling at that moment?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "We are staying actually at Danielle's friend's house.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Where are you guys staying now?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "We've experienced first-hand how it feels and we have a lot of friends in the Black Forest community, friends, family and we just -- we want to give back to them.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "I've also read that you now want to volunteer at these shelters, why?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Yes, how can you look in the eyes of the families of these murdered 6 and 7-year-olds and tell them that we can't do anything when the facts are the facts that in Columbine if we had universal background checks those guys might not have gotten the guns.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Six month have now gone by, nearly 5,000 more Americans have been killed by guns and it seems to me, let's be brutally honest, absolutely nothing has changed and this prompts the question, if nothing changes when 20 children get murdered, when does it change?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "I'm Joe Manchin, I approve this ad because I'll always defend West Virginia.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Remember this TV add?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Yes, you know, it's never made a lot of sense to me.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Let's take an example, Lindsey Graham, who I happen to personally like, but he's very pro-Second Amendment, very pro-gun rights, very anti any new form of gun control or background checks, and yet he's one of the first people to pop up in the last week whole heartedly endorsing the NSA gathering all this date and information about Americans, seemingly oblivious to hypocrisy of that position, when one of his arguments against background check and why should the government have all this information on us?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Well, clearly, the information that they've gleaned from this program has led to some bad guys being stopped from doing bad things.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "But at what risk and damage to the average American privacy, do you think?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, let's start off with Snowden.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Where do you sit?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Well, I think that -- and we've had this over the years and we've had it actually a number of times over the years but there's never been anything quite like this and there's never been -- you know, this is all because of what's happened with all of the e-mails and the twitters and all of -- you know, what's taking place in a computerized world.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Well, China is having a field day because that's true.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Is that not in the public interest?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Well, I was surprised.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Are you surprised by that news?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Well, I don't hear anything.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Yes, I mean, what do you -- what do you hear or think is maybe behind it?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Well, she's getting hit very hard.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "What do you think of Hillary generally and what do you think of her chances if she does run a success in 2016?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Well, I have a great relationship with him.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "If he did run, if he did run, Donald, would you -- would you see yourself endorsing him pretty quickly?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "He's definitely a geek.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Am I overstating things?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "He's a little bit of a know-it-all.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "What is that type?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "That's a great question.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "If you're such a great, you know, campaigner for privacy and everything else, why on earth would you go and work at the NSA?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, what's important to understand is that on this forum that he was posting on, it's very for tech geeks, for IT guys, he posted nearly 800 times.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "The kind of picture I got from what you unearthed about him was just, you know, he's -- he's a guy with a pretty big sense of his own importance in life but that importance in life was quite important in his little world, was nowhere near important enough for him to start making decisions about national security, was it?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "No, I don't think you're unfair but then -- and that's one viable scenario for sure, looking at this as a psychologist, just as another person.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "But am I unfair to say that?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I think the Internet, at least types of communities he is a part of has been broadly sympathetic.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "We all have our view taken from our positions but in the Internet world, it's your world, is he seen as more of a hero than a villain?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "The president has been so supportive of our cause and we're more than happy to work with him and Vice President Biden in their effort to pass some commonsense gun legislation.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Tell me first of all, if you may, Teresa, how did it go today in Washington, and in particular your meeting with the president?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "Well, it makes me feel very sad.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "How does it make you feel?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "It just shows you how screwed up this country has become and how you can see someone walk into an elementary school and use that gun to kill 20 6- and 7-year-olds, to look at them and not even care when you hear them scream, and just open fire, to look at six educators who are there to teach their kids, to teach them how to write and how to do multiplication and add.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What does that tell you about America right now?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Well, I just think more average Americans, though almost 90 percent that seem to agree with gun registration will speak up.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "What do you think it's going to take to persuade the people in Washington to actually take this more seriously than they have done so far?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I've been watching you two now for a few weeks.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "What are you serving up?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "I think if I wasn't a little nervous I wouldn't be -- it wouldn't have a pulse.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Are you feeling the nerves?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Any faults of hers we could dwell on?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "I'll go higher with it.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Fake angry?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Big is the word that comes to mind.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "What is its unique selling points, do you think?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Because you were plunged right in.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "That was the big growing pain for me coming here is, how am I going to do this for five hours when this story is developing in front of me?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "I believe that, you know, to be fair, I think that is the job.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Is that something you've always tried to do?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Come on, tell him.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "With the 4:00 a.m. alarm call every morning?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "But to get ready for it, I've been calling it my spring training.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "And?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I was waking up at 2:15.", "docId": "130613pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "How early?", "qSentId": 571}]